<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Quick Sale &#187; 2 Columns</title>
	<atom:link href="http://quicksale.themerex.net/category/portfolio-masonry/portfolio-masonry-2-columns/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net</link>
	<description>single property</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 07:37:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=4.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Understanding FHA Home Loans</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/understanding-fha-home-loans/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/understanding-fha-home-loans/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 08:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Masonry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Garage]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=737</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Because of lower down payment requirements and less stringent lending standards, FHA loans are popular with mortgage borrowers. Simply stated, an FHA loan is a mortgage insured by the Federal Housing Administration, a government agency within the U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development. Borrowers with FHA loans pay for mortgage insurance, which protects the [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Because of lower down payment requirements and less stringent lending standards, FHA loans are popular with mortgage borrowers. Simply stated, an FHA loan is a mortgage insured by the Federal Housing Administration, a government agency within the U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development. Borrowers with FHA loans pay for mortgage insurance, which protects the lender from a loss if the borrower defaults on the loan. Why people get FHA loans? Because of that insurance, lenders can &#8212; and do &#8212; offer FHA loans at attractive interest rates and with less stringent and more flexible qualification requirements. Minimum credit scores for FHA loans depend on the type of loan the borrower needs. To get a mortgage with a down payment as low as 3.5 percent, the borrower needs a credit score of 580 or higher.</p>
<p>Those with credit scores between 500 and 579 must make down payments of at least 10 percent. People with credit scores under 500 generally are ineligible for FHA loans. The FHA will make allowances under certain circumstances for applicants who have what it calls &#8220;nontraditional credit history or insufficient credit&#8221; if they meet requirements. Ask your FHA lender or an FHA loan specialist if you qualify. For most borrowers, the FHA requires a down payment of just 3.5 percent of the purchase price of the home. That&#8217;s a &#8220;huge attraction,&#8221; says Dennis Geist, senior director of compliance and fair lending at Treliant Risk Advisors and formerly a vice president of government programs for another lender. In late 2014, Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac reduced minimum down payments to 3 percent from 10 percent, but such loans have limited availability. FHA borrowers can use their own savings to make the down payment. But other allowed sources of cash include a gift from a family member, or a grant from a state or local government down payment assistance program.</p>
<p>Because the FHA is not a lender, but rather an insurance fund, borrowers need to get their loan through an FHA-approved lender (as opposed to directly from the FHA). Not all FHA-approved lenders offer the same interest rate and costs &#8212; even on the same FHA loan. Costs, services and underwriting standards will vary among lenders or mortgage brokers, so it&#8217;s important for borrowers to shop around.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/understanding-fha-home-loans/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>To Rent Or Buy? Finance Issues</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/to-rent-or-buy-the-financial-issues/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/to-rent-or-buy-the-financial-issues/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 08:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Masonry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bedroom]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=735</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Owning your own home is a huge commitment, not just to the building you buy and the area you choose to live in, but also to your life (and to another person if you are buying with a loved one or friend). There are many benefits to home ownership. Here are just some of them. [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Owning your own home is a huge commitment, not just to the building you buy and the area you choose to live in, but also to your life (and to another person if you are buying with a loved one or friend).<br />
<strong>There are many benefits to home ownership.</strong> Here are just some of them. Once you’ve paid off your mortgage, your home will be yours and it could be worth far more than you paid for it. If your home increases in value you can use that equity to help you afford a bigger home or to fund a more comfortable retirement if you downsize. When you retire you won’t necessarily have the income you need to keep on paying rent – if you have paid your mortgage off you’ll be living there ‘rent free’. You can spend money improving your home and increasing its value, whereas you can’t alter a rented home without the landlord’s permission. And sometimes it can be cheaper to buy than to rent.<br />
<strong>Potential downsides of owning</strong>. It’s a big financial commitment – you need to be sure you can afford what you’re taking on. Can you afford to buy? When interest rates rise, your repayments will also go up. It’s important to know how much a rise would be. There are ways you can get ready for changes in the rate. You also need to be sure you can afford maintenance costs such as replacing a boiler if it packs up or fixing a leaky roof. If you stretch yourself too much when you buy you may resent not having money for meals out, holidays and entertainment. You have less flexibility than when renting. For example, if you want to move for work or personal reasons selling up and moving on is far more expensive if you own as you’ll have all of the associated estate agency and legal fees. Also bear in mind that it may not always be easy to sell your home – you’ll be dependent on what’s happening in the market. If you’re living with someone else and split up, the process of sorting out the property will be far more complicated and expensive</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/to-rent-or-buy-the-financial-issues/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Building Your Wish-list</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/cheapest-homes-in-america/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/cheapest-homes-in-america/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 08:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Masonry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bedroom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Driveway]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=730</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[There’s a difference between what you need and what you want. We all need a place to eat, sleep and call home, but when the time comes to buy that place, there’s a lot to consider. In a dream world we could envision our perfect home and magically make it happen. But this is reality, [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There’s a difference between what you need and what you want. We all need a place to eat, sleep and call home, but when the time comes to buy that place, there’s a lot to consider. In a dream world we could envision our perfect home and magically make it happen. But this is reality, and in reality we all have budgets and other parameters we must work within, which is why I encourage all of my clients to start with a wish-list. It helps you determine exactly what you need, want, and must-have. It lays down a blueprint for your house hunt and it keeps you in check.</p>
<p>Here are some suggestions to help get you started building your wish-list:</p>
<p>• Make a list of all the things you love and don’t want to give up in the place you’re currently – a kitchen island, a soaker tub, a fireplace – whatever gives you pleasure and makes your house feel like home.</p>
<p>• A wish-list can also be referred to as a “change-list” – meaning, these are all the things about my current living space that must change. So take note of all the things in your current space that you are not happy with and highlight anything that frustrates you to no end.</p>
<p>• Consider how long you’re going to be in this home and what you envision happening in your life during that period. If you’re finally going to get that pet dog you’ve always wanted, then you’ll have to consider that when choosing the property.</p>
<p>• Identify which items you must have now, and which items can be added over time. Maybe you really want a deck in your backyard and you’ve just seen a great house that has everything but.  A deck is something you can add on down the road.</p>
<p>• Consider your wish-list a constantly changing thing. Trust me – once you start looking at properties, you’ll be adding and dropping things from your list. That’s the best part about house hunting – every place you see gives you a better sense of what you’re really looking for.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/cheapest-homes-in-america/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mortgage Rules to Follow</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/mortgage-rules-to-follow/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/mortgage-rules-to-follow/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 08:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Masonry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=728</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Whether this is your first home or fourth, really understanding your mortgage and how it works is crucial. After all, it’ll probably be the biggest loan of your life! What Is A Mortgage? In the most basic sense a mortgage is a loan to buy a property. The process of securing a mortgage means lender [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Whether this is your first home or fourth, really understanding your mortgage and how it works is crucial. After all, it’ll probably be the biggest loan of your life!</p>
<p><strong>What Is A Mortgage?</strong><br />
In the most basic sense a mortgage is a loan to buy a property. The process of securing a mortgage means lender approval based on your income, credit rating and other debt.</p>
<p><strong>Understand Your Fixed Costs</strong><br />
Before you decide what you can—or should—spend on a mortgage it’s important to take stock of your habits and your true fixed costs. Be honest with yourself when putting together your household budget, if you’re going to be miserable without your daily premium cup of coffee, then along with your student debt and car payments, consider that a fixed cost.</p>
<p><strong>Paying Off Your Mortgage</strong><br />
Once you’re approved for a mortgage and buy your home (congratulations!), now you have to actually start paying off the loan. There are several factors involved in this like your interest rate, payment schedule (monthly, twice a month, every two weeks, or weekly) and your amortization period, which is the amount of time you’ve selected to pay back the mortgage (usually ranging from 15-25 years).</p>
<p><strong>Picking The Right Interest Rate</strong><br />
The interest rate at which you select to pay off your mortgage varies from “fixed”—whereby the rate will NOT change for the term of the mortgage, and is generally a bit higher but considered more stable, or “variable” whereby the interest rate can fluctuate with the current state of the market.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/mortgage-rules-to-follow/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>The World of Real Estate Markets</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/the-world-of-real-estate-markets/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/the-world-of-real-estate-markets/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 08:01:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Masonry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=726</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Real estate is &#8220;property consisting of land and the buildings on it, along with its natural resources such as crops, minerals, or water; immovable property of this nature; an interest vested in this (also) an item of real property; (more generally) buildings or housing in general. Also: the business of real estate; the profession of [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Real estate is &#8220;property consisting of land and the buildings on it, along with its natural resources such as crops, minerals, or water; immovable property of this nature; an interest vested in this (also) an item of real property; (more generally) buildings or housing in general. Also: the business of real estate; the profession of buying, selling, or renting land, buildings or housing.<br />
Residential real estate is a type of leased property, containing either a single family or multifamily structure, that is available for occupation for non-business purposes. Residences can be classified by, if, and how they are connected to neighboring residences and land. Different types of housing tenure can be used for the same physical type. For example, connected residents might be owned by a single entity and leased out, or owned separately with an agreement covering the relationship between units and common areas and concerns.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/the-world-of-real-estate-markets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>What&#8217;s a Housing Code?</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/whats-a-housing-code/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/whats-a-housing-code/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 08:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Masonry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Driveway]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=722</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[A a housing code, or a building code, or building control, is a set of rules that specify the minimum standards for constructed objects such as buildings and nonbuilding structures. The main purpose of building codes are to protect public health, safety and general welfare as they relate to the construction and occupancy of buildings [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A a housing code, or a building code, or building control, is a set of rules that specify the minimum standards for constructed objects such as buildings and nonbuilding structures. The main purpose of building codes are to protect public health, safety and general welfare as they relate to the construction and occupancy of buildings and structures. The building code becomes law of a particular jurisdiction when formally enacted by the appropriate governmental or private authority.</p>
<p>Building codes are generally intended to be applied by architects, engineers, constructors and regulators but are also used for various purposes by safety inspectors, environmental scientists, real estate developers, subcontractors, manufacturers of building products and materials, insurance companies, facility managers, tenants, and others. Codes regulating the design and construction of structures where adopted into law. Codes in developed western nations can be quite complex and exhaustive. They began in ancient times and have been developing ever since. In the USA the main codes are the International Commercial or Residential Code [ICC/IRC], electrical codes and plumbing, mechanical codes. Fifty states and the District of Columbia have adopted the I-Codes at the state or jurisdictional level. Other codes may include fire, health, transportation, manufacturing, and other regulations/regulators/testers such as UL; Underwriters Labs. In essence they are minimum standards of design and implementation. Designers use ICC/IRC standards out of substantial reference books during design. Building departments review plans submitted to them before construction, issue permits [or not] and inspectors verify compliance to these standards at the site during construction.</p>
<p>There are often additional codes or sections of the same building code that have more specific requirements that apply to dwellings or places of business and special construction objects such as canopies, signs, pedestrian walkways, parking lots, and radio and television antennas.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/whats-a-housing-code/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fighting Real Estate Fraud</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/fightingreal-estate-fraud/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/fightingreal-estate-fraud/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 07:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Masonry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bedroom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=739</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Fraud and investment scams abound at all levels of the real estate market – whether it be a contractor who charges hundreds of dollars for work not done to an “investment agent” who embezzles hundreds of millions – protecting yourself can require a measure of vigilance and legwork, but it can also come down to [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fraud and investment scams abound at all levels of the real estate market – whether it be a contractor who charges hundreds of dollars for work not done to an “investment agent” who embezzles hundreds of millions – protecting yourself can require a measure of vigilance and legwork, but it can also come down to exercising skepticism and common sense.<br />
<strong>1. Title fraud</strong>.<br />
Although relatively rare, one of the most devastating frauds for property owners is title fraud. This type of fraud starts with identity theft. The scammer will use false documents to pose as the property owner, registers forged documents transferring a property to his or her name, and then gets a new mortgage against the property. After securing a mortgage or line of credit, the criminal takes the cash and leaves the owner on the hook for future payments.<br />
<strong>2. Foreclosure and home-equity fraud.</strong><br />
Criminals and criminal enterprises can take advantage of property owners who find themselves in a cash crunch, being short on funds for liabilities such as mortgage payments or other purposes. Two common scams that exploit a victim’s need for cash are foreclosure fraud and home-equity fraud.<br />
<strong>3. Online rental/sale scams.</strong><br />
In these scams, rental property is advertised (usually at low costs) on online classified sites. The ads use information and photos describing the property that has been “scraped” from legitimate ads, such as those on the MLS. A scammer will impersonate the landlord, property manager or estate agent and will respond to emails and calls from prospective tenants. The scammer indicates he or she is unable to meet a prospective renter at the property, and instead proposes a meeting off site to exchange keys, sign a tenancy agreement and collect rental deposits. Victims may only learn they’ve been duped when they show up at a property to discover that it is already occupied.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/fightingreal-estate-fraud/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of House Hunting</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/the-art-of-house-hunting/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/the-art-of-house-hunting/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 08:12:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Masonry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=743</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[There comes a time when having the freedom to up sticks and move around starts to lose its shine. You begrudge lining someone else’s pockets with rent. You begin to long for something other than beige walls; you dream of having the licence to get hammer-happy put up as many picture hooks as you choose. [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There comes a time when having the freedom to up sticks and move around starts to lose its shine. You begrudge lining someone else’s pockets with rent. You begin to long for something other than beige walls; you dream of having the licence to get hammer-happy put up as many picture hooks as you choose. You start to squirrel away more and more of your Friday Night Out fund for sensible reasons and then, lo and behold, one day you find you have a savings account named ‘Deposit’ and enough in it to begin the House Hunt. You want to own cushions. Life is good.<br />
But how do you begin to tackle the mountainous task of finding your new home? Well, pack your best plimsolls and fetch your guide rope: here are a few important lessons for the house hunt.</p>
<p>1. <strong>Need versus want:</strong> know the difference. Fairly self-explanatory; assess your needs as a priority – three bedrooms would be nice, but two is what you need. A conservatory is a possible future goal, but for now, you can make nice with the neighbours in the front room. A vegetable patch might be an absolute must, pronto, but tea on the lawn can wait until house number two.</p>
<p>2. <strong>Take a camera to every viewing:</strong>  Sometimes you can walk into a house and just know. Most of the time, you can’t. You need to mull it over, compare and contrast and, above all, make an informed decision. Your memory is often coloured by sentiment, so don’t buy a house off the back of it.</p>
<p>3. <strong>Make a wish list:</strong> This is not the same as knowing your needs. Your wish list should comprise what you want to get out of your home. Do you want a project to fix up and make your own, addling oodles and bunches of character as you go? Or are you seeking a sleek, modern and low maintenance property to better suit your busy lifestyle?  </p>
<p>4. <strong>Get a second opinion:</strong> Fresh eyes will see past your rose-tinted view and speak as they find. Very valuable for rescuing you on occasion, but be prepared to justify your own inclinations to buy a home. You’ll either be more certain than ever, or your conviction will wane under scrutiny.</p>
<p>5. <strong>Don’t jump in feet first:</strong>  Get to know the area, get to love it and get inspired by the idea of creating a life in it. From rolling hills and quaint country villages to city landscapes and suburbs in between, the options are there for exploring. Invest some time in getting to know your surroundings before setting up camp and settling down.</p>
<p>6. <strong>Pounds and pennies:</strong> Don’t be tempted to take on more than you can afford. If you’re moving out of the city to save or cut costs, bear in mind your outgoings when calculating how much you can afford to pay for a mortgage. The Victorian Mansion may have to wait until you’re higher up the property ladder…</p>
<p>7.<strong> Think with your head, as well as your heart:</strong> By all means, fall in love with an area, with a community or even with a particular house. But don’t let desperation to make your move lead you into buying the wrong home. The housing market can move quickly, but panic-buying a disaster house, wildly out of your budget and with a laundry list of flaws will only lead to trouble.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/the-art-of-house-hunting/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Title Insurance: Who Needs It?</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/title-insurance-who-needs-it/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/title-insurance-who-needs-it/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 08:04:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Masonry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=732</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Who needs title insurance? Anyone who owns a house! Title insurance is a policy of insurance that provides coverage for the title-related risks associated with real estate transactions. It is designed to cover the unpredictable or undetectable issues such as forgery, fraud, missing heirs, etc. that can affect rights of ownership. Because it is insurance, [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Who needs title insurance?  Anyone who owns a house!  Title insurance is a policy of insurance that provides coverage for the title-related risks associated with real estate transactions.  It is designed to cover the unpredictable or undetectable issues such as forgery, fraud, missing heirs, etc. that can affect rights of ownership.  Because it is insurance, a title insurance policy moves the risk associated with title from the homebuyer, the lending institution or the lawyer, to the title insurer. If there is a problem with title that only becomes known after closing, the title insurer may rectify the problem or compensate the title insurance policyholder, provided the type of problem that surfaces is covered by the title insurance policy.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/title-insurance-who-needs-it/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Broker&#8217;s Responsibility</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/a-brokers-responsibility/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/a-brokers-responsibility/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 06:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Masonry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bedroom]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=741</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[A broker is an individual or party (brokerage firm) that arranges transactions between a buyer and a seller for a commission when the deal is executed. A broker who also acts as a seller or as a buyer becomes a principal party to the deal. Distinguish agent—one who acts on behalf of a principal. In [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A broker is an individual or party (brokerage firm) that arranges transactions between a buyer and a seller for a commission when the deal is executed. A broker who also acts as a seller or as a buyer becomes a principal party to the deal. Distinguish agent—one who acts on behalf of a principal. In general, a broker is an independent agent used extensively in some industries. A broker&#8217;s prime responsibility is to bring sellers and buyers together and thus a broker is the third-person facilitator between a buyer and a seller. An example would be a real estate broker who facilitates the sale of a property.Brokers also can furnish market information regarding prices, products, and market conditions. Brokers may represent either the seller (90% of the time) or the buyer (10%) but not both at the same time. An example would be a stockbroker, who makes the sale or purchase of securities on behalf of his client. Brokers play a huge role in the sale of stocks, bonds, and other financial services.</p>
<p>There are advantages to using a broker. First, they know their market and have already established relations with prospective accounts. Brokers have the tools and resources to reach the largest possible base of buyers. They then screen these potential buyers for revenue that would support the potential acquisition. An individual producer, on the other hand, especially one new in the market, probably will not have the same access to customers as a broker. Another benefit of using a broker is cost—they might be cheaper in smaller markets, with smaller accounts, or with a limited line of products. Before hiring a broker, it may be considered prudent to research the requirements relating to someone using the title. Some titles, such as Real Estate Brokers, often have strict state requirements for using the term, while others, such as Aircraft Brokers, typically have no formal licensing or training requirements.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/a-brokers-responsibility/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
