<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Quick Sale</title>
	<atom:link href="http://quicksale.themerex.net/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net</link>
	<description>single property</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 07:37:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=4.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Post formats &#8211; Status</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/post-formats-status/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/post-formats-status/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 07:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Classic Style Large]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=1940</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Nothing in life is to be feared, it is only to be understood. Now is the time to understand more, so that we may fear less&#8230;]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nothing in life is to be feared, it is only to be understood. Now is the time to understand more, so that we may fear less&#8230;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/post-formats-status/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Post With Image</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/new-post-with-image/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/new-post-with-image/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2015 13:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style Large]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style Small]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cottage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bedroom]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=525</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[ThemeRex is a studio that aims to make their users’ experience easier and much more pleasant. You probalby won’t have a better opportunity to make sure of their competence, as well as friendliness towards their customers. Vast experience and understanding of each product’s peculiarities let ThemeRex create outstanding business solutions.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ThemeRex is a studio that aims to make their users’ experience easier and much more pleasant. You probalby won’t have a better opportunity to make sure of their competence, as well as friendliness towards their customers. Vast experience and understanding of each product’s peculiarities let ThemeRex create outstanding business solutions. <blockquote class="sc_quote  margin_bottom_mini sc_quote_style_1" style="margin-top:5px;"><p>Always bear in mind that your own resolution to succeed is more important than any other.</p></blockquote> ThemeRex is doing their best to grant each owner of their themes with maximum opportunities to present their individuality, show their achievements, and establish the best contact with their audience. Using their rich experience, world’s innovations and their own web solutions the ThemeRex team creates templates that will solve your business’s tasks at maximum degree.</p>
<h4>High Professionalism</h4>
<p>Many year experience and hundreds of successful projects have made ThemeRex a professional on the web area. Within this period of time, the company has gone through a serious evolution from amateurs to leaders. We create templates for your websites that will increase your reputation and highlight your professionalism and leadership. <div class="sc_section sc_alignleft columns1_2" style="margin-top:5px !important;margin-bottom:10px !important;"> <figure class="sc_image  sc_image_shape_square"><img src="http://quicksale.themerex.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/home-m-3.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><span>Title of Image</span></figcaption></figure> </div> Purchasing products from ThemeRex means entrusting your reputation to one of the best web-studios. ThemeRex company does its work with its customer in mind. That is why you are getting the best product that will perfectly suit your needs.</p>
<p>Not only does ThemeRex create bright, eye-catching designs and do premium quality code, they provide great support to their customers. ThemeRex technical support is always there to assist their users with all their technical questions regarding ThemeRex products. We speak clear language understood by everyone. You need our assistance &#8211; we happily help you. Use comments to ask pre-sale questions, and Ticket System to get any help with our products. Our support team is always happy to help our customers. Whether it is assistance with installation or just configuration, we are here to help.  </p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/new-post-with-image/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Post Formats &#8211; Quote post</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/post-formats-quote-post/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/post-formats-quote-post/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 10:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style Large]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Masonry demo]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=601</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[&#160;]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[ <blockquote cite="#" class="sc_quote sc_quote_style_1"><p>Look deep into nature, and then you will understand everything better.</p><p class="sc_quote_title"><a href="#">Albert Einstein</a></p></blockquote> &nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/post-formats-quote-post/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Who Should Buy &#8216;Rent To Own&#8217;</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/who-should-buy-rent-to-own/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/who-should-buy-rent-to-own/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2014 14:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Driveway]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Living room]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=989</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Over the years, the rent-to-own industry has grown to include fine art, bicycles, storage sheds, riding lawn mowers, and even wheels and tires. Here, we take a brief look at how rent to own works, and what consumers should know about it. There are currently about 10,100 rent-to-own stores in operation in the U.S., Mexico [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over the years, the rent-to-own industry has grown to include fine art, bicycles, storage sheds, riding lawn mowers, and even wheels and tires. Here, we take a brief look at how rent to own works, and what consumers should know about it.</p>
<p>There are currently about 10,100 rent-to-own stores in operation in the U.S., Mexico and Canada, serving 4.8 million customers each year. As a renter, you enter into an agreement with one of these stores, make regular rent payments – either by the week or month – and after a predetermined number of payments, the item is yours to keep. Unlike a normal retail credit sale, there are no credit-history checks, and you can return the item at any time. Many stores promote that “everyone’s approved.” </p>
<p>Consumers can also take the rent-to-own route to purchase homes and automobiles. These agreements, however, differ from those found in rent-to-own stores. The primary difference is that with a home or car, the renter must make a “down payment” of sorts: In a real estate transaction, this is referred to as option money, and it’s cash paid by the buyer to the seller for the option (or right) to purchase the house in the future. You pay rent for a set period of time (usually one to three years), and at the end of the lease, you can exercise your right to buy the house (for a price that is established in advance, or at the current market value, whichever is stated in the contract). If you decide not to purchase the house, you can walk away, but you lose the option money and any portion of the rent you paid that earned you a credit towards the purchase price.</p>
<p>Even though rent-to-own stores typically don’t represent the best deal – for either outright purchases or rentals – they may be a good option if you don’t plan on needing an item for very long. If you are renting an apartment for a just a few months, for example, it might make sense to rent your furniture, TV and other items. It’s also a reasonable option if you have bad or nonexistent credit and you are unable to qualify for a loan or line of credit.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/who-should-buy-rent-to-own/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Commercial Real Estate Loans</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/commercial-real-estate-loans/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/commercial-real-estate-loans/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2014 14:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Living room]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=987</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[A commercial mortgage is a mortgage loan secured by commercial property, such as an office building, shopping center, industrial warehouse, or apartment complex. The proceeds from a commercial mortgage are typically used to acquire, refinance, or redevelop commercial property. Commercial mortgages are structured to meet the needs of the borrower and the lender. Key terms [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A commercial mortgage is a mortgage loan secured by commercial property, such as an office building, shopping center, industrial warehouse, or apartment complex. The proceeds from a commercial mortgage are typically used to acquire, refinance, or redevelop commercial property.</p>
<p>Commercial mortgages are structured to meet the needs of the borrower and the lender. Key terms include the loan amount (sometimes referred to as &#8220;loan proceeds&#8221;), interest rate, term (sometimes referred to as the &#8220;maturity&#8221;), amortization schedule, and prepayment flexibility. Commercial mortgages are generally subject to extensive underwriting and due diligence prior to closing. The lender&#8217;s underwriting process may include a financial review of the property and the property owner (or &#8220;sponsor&#8221;), as well as commissioning and review of various third-party reports, such as an appraisal.</p>
<p>There were $3.1 trillion of commercial and multifamily mortgages outstanding in the U.S. as of June 30, 2013. Of these mortgages, approximately 49% were held by banks, 18% were held by asset-backed trusts (issuers of CMBS), 12% were held by government-sponsored enterprises and Agency and GSE-backed mortgage pools, and 10% were held by life insurance companies. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/commercial-real-estate-loans/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Real Estate Traps To Avoid</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/real-estate-traps-to-avoid-2/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/real-estate-traps-to-avoid-2/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2014 14:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bedroom]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=984</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Since a home buyer apportions the bulk of his savings and income to a single investment, he wants to save as much as possible. Property developers exploit this penny-pinching penchant by offering various innovative schemes that are laden with freebies. At face value, most of these options appear tempting, but when you scrub off the [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since a home buyer apportions the bulk of his savings and income to a single investment, he wants to save as much as possible. Property developers exploit this penny-pinching penchant by offering various innovative schemes that are laden with freebies. At face value, most of these options appear tempting, but when you scrub off the gloss, you&#8217;ll discover that they are riddled with traps.<br />
Starting a search without clearly knowing what you want and then “hoping the ideal property will turn up!” With this approach, chances are you will waste plenty of time and energy and possibly purchasing something that doesn’t meet your needs or is beyond your budget!</p>
<p>Not doing the hard yards – the temptation is to cut corners on your research because you’re sick and tired of giving up your weekends looking at property but this is likely to be one of the biggest financial decisions you’ll ever make so you want to get it right! The better you know the area, the better you will become familiar with prices and importantly you’ll know how to spot great value when you see it!<br />
5Forgetting about buying costs – remember to add stamp duty and settlement costs into the mix. This is usually up to an additional 5% on top of the purchase price that needs to be factored in when setting your budget.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/real-estate-traps-to-avoid-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Selling Your House?</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/selling-your-house-2/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/selling-your-house-2/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2014 14:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Garage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Living room]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=982</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The peak homebuying season may be over, but there are still steps you can take to ensure a speedy sale. Setting the right price and making an excellent first impression are both essential to attracting buyers, but what else can you do to get the offers rolling in? Here are 10 tips to help you [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The peak homebuying season may be over, but there are still steps you can take to ensure a speedy sale. Setting the right price and making an excellent first impression are both essential to attracting buyers, but what else can you do to get the offers rolling in? Here are 10 tips to help you sell your home as quickly as possible – even in the offseason.<br />
<strong>Price it right from the start.</strong> Sellers often think they should start the asking price high and then lower it later if the house fails to sell. But that can result in a slower sale – sometimes even at a lower price. The first 30 days’ activity of your house being on the market is always the best activity you’re going to see.<br />
<strong>Update the interior and exterior.</strong> New fixtures, fresh paint and updated landscaping are all fairly easy and affordable ways to give your home a makeover. It’s got to look up to the current market conditions and what’s in style.<br />
<strong>Stage the house to show how the rooms are supposed to be used.</strong> If you have odd rooms with no obvious role, give them one. An odd alcove off the kitchen could be staged as an office or a pantry, for example.<br />
<strong>Make the property easy to show.</strong> The more flexible you are about visits, the more people will be able to see your home. Be ready for prospective visitors early in the morning, at night and on weekends, with little notice. Also, leave when the house is shown so would-be buyers can feel free to move about without feeling like intruders and discuss the home&#8217;s pros and cons honestly.<br />
<strong>Make sure your listing is on all the major online portals.</strong> This is usually part of an agent’s service, but it doesn’t hurt to double-check that your listing is on the largest real estate websites. It also helps if your agent showcases the home on social media. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/selling-your-house-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>To Buy or Not To Buy</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/nostrud-exercitation-ullamco/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/nostrud-exercitation-ullamco/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2014 14:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Driveway]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kitchen]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=980</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Owning your own home is a huge commitment, not just to the building you buy and the area you choose to live in, but also to your life (and to another person if you are buying with a loved one or friend). There are many benefits to home ownership. Here are just some of them. [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Owning your own home is a huge commitment, not just to the building you buy and the area you choose to live in, but also to your life (and to another person if you are buying with a loved one or friend).<br />
<strong>There are many benefits to home ownership.</strong> Here are just some of them. Once you’ve paid off your mortgage, your home will be yours and it could be worth far more than you paid for it. If your home increases in value you can use that equity to help you afford a bigger home or to fund a more comfortable retirement if you downsize. When you retire you won’t necessarily have the income you need to keep on paying rent – if you have paid your mortgage off you’ll be living there ‘rent free’. You can spend money improving your home and increasing its value, whereas you can’t alter a rented home without the landlord’s permission. And sometimes it can be cheaper to buy than to rent.<br />
<strong>Potential downsides of owning</strong>. It’s a big financial commitment – you need to be sure you can afford what you’re taking on. Can you afford to buy? When interest rates rise, your repayments will also go up. It’s important to know how much a rise would be. There are ways you can get ready for changes in the rate. You also need to be sure you can afford maintenance costs such as replacing a boiler if it packs up or fixing a leaky roof. If you stretch yourself too much when you buy you may resent not having money for meals out, holidays and entertainment. You have less flexibility than when renting. For example, if you want to move for work or personal reasons selling up and moving on is far more expensive if you own as you’ll have all of the associated estate agency and legal fees. Also bear in mind that it may not always be easy to sell your home – you’ll be dependent on what’s happening in the market. If you’re living with someone else and split up, the process of sorting out the property will be far more complicated and expensive</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/nostrud-exercitation-ullamco/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Freehold Vs. Condo</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/freehold-vs-condo/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/freehold-vs-condo/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2014 14:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bedroom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Garage]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=978</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Condos can be a great choice for many people, including first-time buyers looking to get into the market and build equity. A condo unit can be a good starting point since it is usually less expensive to own and carry than a traditional house. Condos can also be the right decision for people making their [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Condos can be a great choice for many people, including first-time buyers looking to get into the market and build equity. A condo unit can be a good starting point since it is usually less expensive to own and carry than a traditional house. Condos can also be the right decision for people making their choice based on lifestyle. These buyers primarily choose this type of home because there is no yard work, snow removal or roofing repairs to be done, while others are looking for the extra security that comes with being high up in a secure building. </p>
<p>Condominium ownership offers many advantages, such as the potential to build equity, title, and privacy within your unit. With a condo, you can count on the fact that your property is being well maintained with little effort on your part. </p>
<p>On the other hand, freehold units offer other advantages over the condominium option. You have more freedom to alter your property to suit your needs, and since you are responsible for upkeep, you have a bit more control over your maintenance costs. You can keep expenses down by cutting your own lawn and shoveling your own drive. You will have to budget accordingly for big expenses like a new roof or furnace. </p>
<p>Condos have rules and by-laws that govern such things as pets and what colour your neighbour can paint his garage, and by law a portion of the maintenance fee goes towards a reserve fund. Sometimes, the need for such rules, by-laws and a reserve fund become evident when the complex begins to age and can negatively affect resale values. There&#8217;s a lot to consider when choosing a condo or freehold home; be sure to ask your realtor for help.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/freehold-vs-condo/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of House Hunting</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/the-art-of-house-hunting-2/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/the-art-of-house-hunting-2/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2014 14:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Living room]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=975</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[There comes a time when having the freedom to up sticks and move around starts to lose its shine. You begrudge lining someone else’s pockets with rent. You begin to long for something other than beige walls; you dream of having the licence to get hammer-happy put up as many picture hooks as you choose. [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There comes a time when having the freedom to up sticks and move around starts to lose its shine. You begrudge lining someone else’s pockets with rent. You begin to long for something other than beige walls; you dream of having the licence to get hammer-happy put up as many picture hooks as you choose. You start to squirrel away more and more of your Friday Night Out fund for sensible reasons and then, lo and behold, one day you find you have a savings account named ‘Deposit’ and enough in it to begin the House Hunt. You want to own cushions. Life is good.<br />
But how do you begin to tackle the mountainous task of finding your new home? Well, pack your best plimsolls and fetch your guide rope: here are a few important lessons for the house hunt.</p>
<p>1. <strong>Need versus want:</strong> know the difference. Fairly self-explanatory; assess your needs as a priority – three bedrooms would be nice, but two is what you need. A conservatory is a possible future goal, but for now, you can make nice with the neighbours in the front room. A vegetable patch might be an absolute must, pronto, but tea on the lawn can wait until house number two.</p>
<p>2. <strong>Take a camera to every viewing:</strong>  Sometimes you can walk into a house and just know. Most of the time, you can’t. You need to mull it over, compare and contrast and, above all, make an informed decision. Your memory is often coloured by sentiment, so don’t buy a house off the back of it.</p>
<p>3. <strong>Make a wish list:</strong> This is not the same as knowing your needs. Your wish list should comprise what you want to get out of your home. Do you want a project to fix up and make your own, addling oodles and bunches of character as you go? Or are you seeking a sleek, modern and low maintenance property to better suit your busy lifestyle?  </p>
<p>4. <strong>Get a second opinion:</strong> Fresh eyes will see past your rose-tinted view and speak as they find. Very valuable for rescuing you on occasion, but be prepared to justify your own inclinations to buy a home. You’ll either be more certain than ever, or your conviction will wane under scrutiny.</p>
<p>5. <strong>Don’t jump in feet first:</strong>  Get to know the area, get to love it and get inspired by the idea of creating a life in it. From rolling hills and quaint country villages to city landscapes and suburbs in between, the options are there for exploring. Invest some time in getting to know your surroundings before setting up camp and settling down.</p>
<p>6. <strong>Pounds and pennies:</strong> Don’t be tempted to take on more than you can afford. If you’re moving out of the city to save or cut costs, bear in mind your outgoings when calculating how much you can afford to pay for a mortgage. The Victorian Mansion may have to wait until you’re higher up the property ladder…</p>
<p>7.<strong> Think with your head, as well as your heart:</strong> By all means, fall in love with an area, with a community or even with a particular house. But don’t let desperation to make your move lead you into buying the wrong home. The housing market can move quickly, but panic-buying a disaster house, wildly out of your budget and with a laundry list of flaws will only lead to trouble.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/the-art-of-house-hunting-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
