<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Quick Sale &#187; 2 Columns</title>
	<atom:link href="http://quicksale.themerex.net/category/portfolio-classic/portfolio-classic-2-columns/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net</link>
	<description>single property</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 07:37:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=4.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Working With A Realtor</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/working-with-a-realtor/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/working-with-a-realtor/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 14:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Attic]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=799</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[A Realtor is a broker or agent who is a member of the Board of Realtors, an organization that follows a code of ethics beyond state license laws. It is realtors who sponsor the Multiple Listing Service to which every real estate agent in the country is beholden for listing or searching prospects. Shopping for [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Realtor is a broker or agent who is a member of the Board of Realtors, an organization that follows a code of ethics beyond state license laws. It is realtors who sponsor the Multiple Listing Service to which every real estate agent in the country is beholden for listing or searching prospects. Shopping for a real estate agent should be no different from searching for any other professional, like a lawyer or an accountant. If you know someone in the business &#8211; such as an escrow officer, title representative, or homeowners&#8217; insurance salesperson &#8211; ask for a recommendation. When interviewing prospective agents, ask questions about the local market and expect informed answers on the spot. If they have to call you back after they check the listings, it could be they&#8217;re not doing due diligence.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/working-with-a-realtor/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>What&#8217;s FHA Home Loans</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/whats-fha-home-loans/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/whats-fha-home-loans/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 14:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=789</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[An FHA insured loan is a US Federal Housing Administration mortgage insurance backed mortgage loan which is provided by a FHA-approved lender. FHA insured loans are a type of federal assistance and have historically allowed lower income Americans to borrow money for the purchase of a home that they would not otherwise be able to [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An FHA insured loan is a US Federal Housing Administration mortgage insurance backed mortgage loan which is provided by a FHA-approved lender. FHA insured loans are a type of federal assistance and have historically allowed lower income Americans to borrow money for the purchase of a home that they would not otherwise be able to afford. To obtain mortgage insurance from the Federal Housing Administration, an upfront mortgage insurance premium (UFMIP) equal to 1.75 percent of the base loan amount at closing is required, and is normally financed into the total loan amount by the lender and paid to FHA on the borrower&#8217;s behalf. There is also a monthly mortgage insurance premium (MIP) which varies based on the amortization term and loan-to-value ratio.</p>
<p>The program originated during the Great Depression of the 1930s, when the rates of foreclosures and defaults rose sharply, and the program was intended to provide lenders with sufficient insurance. Some FHA programs were subsidized by the government, but the goal was to make it self-supporting, based on insurance premiums paid by borrowers. Over time, private mortgage insurance (PMI) companies came into play, and now FHA primarily serves people who cannot afford a conventional down payment or otherwise do not qualify for PMI. The program has since this time been modified to accommodate the heightened recession.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/whats-fha-home-loans/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 3 Mortgage Mistakes</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/top-3-mortgage-mistakes/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/top-3-mortgage-mistakes/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 14:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Garage]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=790</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[During the 2007-2009 financial crisis, the United States economy crumbled because of a problem with mortgage foreclosures. Borrowers all over the nation had trouble paying their mortgages. At the time, eight out of 10 borrowers were trying to refinance their mortgages. Even high end homeowners were having trouble with foreclosures. Why were so many citizens [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>During the 2007-2009 financial crisis, the United States economy crumbled because of a problem with mortgage foreclosures. Borrowers all over the nation had trouble paying their mortgages. At the time, eight out of 10 borrowers were trying to refinance their mortgages. Even high end homeowners were having trouble with foreclosures. Why were so many citizens having trouble with their mortgages? Let&#8217;s take a look at the biggest mortgage mistakes that homeowners make.</p>
<p><strong>1. Adjustable Rate Mortgages</strong><br />
Adjustable rate mortgages seem like a homeowners dream. An adjustable rate mortgage starts you off with a low interest rate for the first two to five years. They allow you to buy a larger house than you can normally qualify for and have lower payments that you can afford. After two to five years the interest rate resets to a higher market rate. That&#8217;s no problem because borrowers can just take the equity out of their homes and refinance to a lower rate once it resets.</p>
<p>Well, it doesn&#8217;t always work out that way. When housing prices drop, borrowers tend to find that they are unable to refinance their existing loans. This leaves many borrowers facing high mortgage payments that are two to three times their original payments. The dream of home ownership quickly becomes a nightmare.</p>
<p><strong>2. No Down Payment</strong><br />
During the subprime crisis, many companies were offering borrowers no down payment loans to borrowers. The purpose of a down payment is twofold. First, it increases the amount of equity that you have in your home and reduces the amount of money that you owe on a home. Second, a down payment makes sure that you have some skin in the game. Borrowers that place down a large down payment are much more likely to try everything possible to make their mortgage payments since they do not want to lose their investment. Many borrowers who put little to nothing down on their homes find themselves upside down on their mortgage and end up just walking away. They owe more money than the home is worth. The more a borrower owes, the more likely they are to walk away.</p>
<p><strong>3. Liar Loans</strong><br />
The phrase &#8220;liar loans&#8221; leaves a bad taste in your mouth. Liar loans were incredibly popular during the real estate boom prior to the subprime meltdown that began in 2007. Mortgage lenders were quick to hand them out and borrowers were quick to accept them. A liar loan is a loan that requires little to no documentation. Liar loans do not require verification. The loan is based on the borrower&#8217;s stated income, stated assets and stated expenses.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/top-3-mortgage-mistakes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tips For Homeowners</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/tips-for-homeowners/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/tips-for-homeowners/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 14:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=796</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Homeowners&#8217; insurance isn&#8217;t a luxury, it&#8217;s a necessity. In fact, most mortgage companies won&#8217;t make a loan or finance a residential real estate transaction unless the buyer provides proof of coverage for the full or fair value of the property (most of the time this is the purchase price). The good news is that although [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Homeowners&#8217; insurance isn&#8217;t a luxury, it&#8217;s a necessity. In fact, most mortgage companies won&#8217;t make a loan or finance a residential real estate transaction unless the buyer provides proof of coverage for the full or fair value of the property (most of the time this is the purchase price). The good news is that although you can&#8217;t (and shouldn&#8217;t) avoid purchasing homeowners&#8217; insurance, there are ways to minimize the cost: Maintain a security system and smoke alarms (A burglar alarm that is monitored by a central station, or that is tied directly to a local police station, will help lower the homeowner&#8217;s annual premiums, perhaps by 5% or more); look for multiple policy discounts (many insurance companies give a discount of 10% or more to their customers that maintain other insurance contracts under the same roof (such as auto or health insurance)); pay jff your mortgage (obviously this is easier said than done, but homeowners that pay off their mortgage debts will most likely see their premiums drop) </p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/tips-for-homeowners/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tips For Buying a House</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/tips-for-buying-a-house/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/tips-for-buying-a-house/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 14:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Attic]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=794</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Buying a house can be a daunting task, even for someone who has owned several homes. Here aresome helpful hints for the first time property buyers:]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Buying a house can be a daunting task, even for someone who has owned several homes. Here aresome helpful hints for the first time property buyers: <ol class="sc_list sc_list_style_ol"> <li class="sc_list_item odd first">Use your online resources. Almost every state and local government has a website where you can research real estate information. The data on home sales, taxes, and neighborhoods is invaluable when you are shopping for a home.</li> <li class="sc_list_item even">Be realistic about how much you can spend.Try to buy a home in a price range that allows you to put down 20%. If you put down less than this, you will have to pay PMI (private mortgage insurance) to protect the lender in case you default on the loan.</li> <li class="sc_list_item odd">Shop for a home in the winter, preferably around the holidays. Since most people just aren&#8217;t interested in buying a home whenthey are trying to deal with the holidays, you can pretty much be one of the few buyers out there.</li> <li class="sc_list_item even">Always have a home inspection. Most people know this fact already, but it is really important in areas with a hot real estate market. It can be easy to get caught up in bidding wars, and to want to get a house at all costs</li> </ol> ]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/tips-for-buying-a-house/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Home Inspection</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/the-home-inspection/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/the-home-inspection/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 14:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Attic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basement]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=813</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[A home inspection is a limited, non-invasive examination of the condition of a home, often in connection with the sale of that home. Home inspections are usually conducted by a home inspector who has the training and certifications to perform such inspections. The inspector prepares and delivers to the client a written report of findings. [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A home inspection is a limited, non-invasive examination of the condition of a home, often in connection with the sale of that home. Home inspections are usually conducted by a home inspector who has the training and certifications to perform such inspections. The inspector prepares and delivers to the client a written report of findings. The client then uses the knowledge gained to make informed decisions about their pending real estate purchase. The home inspector describes the condition of the home at the time of inspection but does not guarantee future condition, efficiency, or life expectancy of systems or components.</p>
<p>A home inspector is sometimes confused with a real estate appraiser. A home inspector determines the condition of a structure, whereas an appraiser determines the value of a property. In the United States, although not all states or municipalities regulate home inspectors, there are various professional associations for home inspectors that provide education, training, and networking opportunities. A professional home inspection is an examination of the current condition of a house. It is not an inspection to verify compliance with appropriate codes; building inspection is a term often used for building code compliance inspections in the United States. A similar but more complicated inspection of commercial buildings is a property condition assessment. Home inspections identify problems but building diagnostics identifies solutions to the found problems and there predicted outcomes.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/the-home-inspection/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Best Mortgage Rates</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/getting-the-best-mortgage-rates/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/getting-the-best-mortgage-rates/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 14:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Attic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kitchen]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=820</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[You want to purchase a home. For most people that means getting a mortgage. This is not the time to let somebody else do the shopping for you. Here&#8217;s why: The terms you get can make a sizable difference in what you pay to borrow the same amount of money. On a $250,000 home, one-quarter [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You want to purchase a home. For most people that means getting a mortgage. This is not the time to let somebody else do the shopping for you. Here&#8217;s why: The terms you get can make a sizable difference in what you pay to borrow the same amount of money. On a $250,000 home, one-quarter of a point could mean an extra $12,000 or more paid in interest over the life of the loan. <ul class="sc_list sc_list_style_arrows"> <li class="sc_list_item icon-right-open-mini odd first">If you’re looking for a home right now, getting your finances in great shape may be tough. On the other hand, if you’re just thinking ahead, read closely.</li> <li class="sc_list_item icon-right-open-mini even">Just like any other high-dollar purchase, banks will fight for the business of qualified buyers. There are plenty of websites that will help you collect quotes from lenders.</li> <li class="sc_list_item icon-right-open-mini odd">If your down payment is less than 20% you’re considered higher risk. PMI, or private mortgage insurance, lowers the risk for the lender but here’s the catch: You have to pay for it and that can add thousands of dollars to what it costs to carry the loan. Expect to pay 0.5% to 1% of the entire loan each year.</li> <li class="sc_list_item icon-right-open-mini even">Let’s say you get the most amazing mortgage deal. Congratulations, but move fast. The interest rate – and possibly other conditions – are locked in for a set amount of time. You have to close within the lock period or risk losing the deal. Don’t procrastinate.</li> </ul> ]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/getting-the-best-mortgage-rates/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Step-by-Step Buying</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/step-by-step-home-buying/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/step-by-step-home-buying/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 14:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=795</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[First of all, have your credit checked. Homebuyers to have their credit checked six months before buying a place to make sure their FICO score is where it needs to be. Know what you can afford. Realtors insist that prospective homebuyers “contact a lender and be pre-approved so they know the price of the house [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>First of all, have your credit checked. Homebuyers to have their credit checked six months before buying a place to make sure their FICO score is where it needs to be.<br />
Know what you can afford. Realtors insist that prospective homebuyers “contact a lender and be pre-approved so they know the price of the house they can afford and won’t be disappointed that they can’t go into the price range they were originally considering.” According to many agents, most people don’t get pre-approved, which usually winds up wasting time and causing problems down the line.<br />
Look into location. If you’re going to be in this home for any length of time, look into school districts and other things that may not matter to you yet, but could eventually. Also, find out what your city or county taxes would be, as well as if your community has Homeowners’ or Condo Association dues.<br />
Think twice before buying a home on your own. Buying a home requires real estate and legal savvy, as well as the confidence to negotiate the final price.<br />
Have the house inspected. Once you find a place, have a home inspection done to find out what is wrong with the place. Even if the person isn’t going to fix it, you need to know that before you make the decision to buy the house.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/step-by-step-home-buying/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reverse Mortgages</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/reverse-mortgages-2/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/reverse-mortgages-2/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 17:39:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=712</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[A reverse mortgage is a home loan that provides cash payments based on home equity. Homeowners normally &#8220;defer payment of the loan until they die, sell, or move out of the home.&#8221; Upon the death of homeowners, their heirs either give up ownership to the home or must refinance the home to purchase the title [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A reverse mortgage is a home loan that provides cash payments based on home equity. Homeowners normally &#8220;defer payment of the loan until they die, sell, or move out of the home.&#8221; Upon the death of homeowners, their heirs either give up ownership to the home or must refinance the home to purchase the title from the reverse mortgage company. Specific rules for reverse mortgage transactions vary depending on the laws of the jurisdiction.</p>
<p>In a conventional mortgage, the homeowner makes a monthly payment to the lender. After each payment, the homeowner&#8217;s equity increases by the amount of the principal included in the payment. In a reverse mortgage, a homeowner is not required to make monthly payments. If payments are not made, interest is added to the loan&#8217;s balance. Although the &#8220;rising loan balance can eventually grow to exceed the value of the home,&#8221; &#8220;the borrower (or the borrower’s estate) is generally not required to repay any additional loan balance in excess of the value of the home.&#8221; In Canada the loan balance cannot exceed the fair market value of the home by law.</p>
<p>Regulators and academics have given mixed commentary on the reverse mortgage market. Some economists argue that reverse mortgages allow seniors to smooth out their income and consumption patterns over time, and thus may provide welfare benefits. However, regulatory authorities, such as the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau, argue that reverse mortgages are &#8220;complex products and difficult for consumers to understand,&#8221; especially in light of &#8220;misleading advertising,&#8221; low-quality counseling, and &#8220;risk of fraud and other scams.&#8221; Moreover, the Bureau claims that many consumers do not use reverse mortgages for the positive, consumption-smoothing purposes advanced by economists. In Canada the borrower must seek independent legal advice before being approved for a reverse mortgage.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/reverse-mortgages-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Renting to Own</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/renting-to-own/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/renting-to-own/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 14:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basement]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=821</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Rent-to-own, also known as rental-purchase, is a type of legally documented transaction under which tangible property, such as furniture, consumer electronics and home appliances, is leased in exchange for a weekly or monthly payment, with the option to purchase at some point during the agreement. A rent-to-own transaction differs from a traditional lease, in that [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Rent-to-own, also known as rental-purchase, is a type of legally documented transaction under which tangible property, such as furniture, consumer electronics and home appliances, is leased in exchange for a weekly or monthly payment, with the option to purchase at some point during the agreement.</p>
<p>A rent-to-own transaction differs from a traditional lease, in that the lessee can purchase the leased item at any time during the agreement (in a traditional lease the lessee has no such right), and from a hire purchase/installment plan, in that the lessee can terminate the agreement by simply returning the property (in a hire purchase the buyer has a limited time, if any, to cancel the agreement).</p>
<p>The usage of rent-to-own transactions began in the United Kingdom and Europe, and first appeared in the United States during the 1950s and 1960s. While rent-to-own terminology is most commonly associated with consumer goods transactions, the term is sometimes used in connection with real estate transactions.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/renting-to-own/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
