<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Quick Sale &#187; 3 Columns + sidebar</title>
	<atom:link href="http://quicksale.themerex.net/category/classic-style/classic-3-columns-sidebar/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net</link>
	<description>single property</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 07:37:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=4.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>New Post With Image</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/new-post-with-image/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/new-post-with-image/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2015 13:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style Large]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style Small]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cottage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bedroom]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=525</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[ThemeRex is a studio that aims to make their users’ experience easier and much more pleasant. You probalby won’t have a better opportunity to make sure of their competence, as well as friendliness towards their customers. Vast experience and understanding of each product’s peculiarities let ThemeRex create outstanding business solutions.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ThemeRex is a studio that aims to make their users’ experience easier and much more pleasant. You probalby won’t have a better opportunity to make sure of their competence, as well as friendliness towards their customers. Vast experience and understanding of each product’s peculiarities let ThemeRex create outstanding business solutions. <blockquote class="sc_quote  margin_bottom_mini sc_quote_style_1" style="margin-top:5px;"><p>Always bear in mind that your own resolution to succeed is more important than any other.</p></blockquote> ThemeRex is doing their best to grant each owner of their themes with maximum opportunities to present their individuality, show their achievements, and establish the best contact with their audience. Using their rich experience, world’s innovations and their own web solutions the ThemeRex team creates templates that will solve your business’s tasks at maximum degree.</p>
<h4>High Professionalism</h4>
<p>Many year experience and hundreds of successful projects have made ThemeRex a professional on the web area. Within this period of time, the company has gone through a serious evolution from amateurs to leaders. We create templates for your websites that will increase your reputation and highlight your professionalism and leadership. <div class="sc_section sc_alignleft columns1_2" style="margin-top:5px !important;margin-bottom:10px !important;"> <figure class="sc_image  sc_image_shape_square"><img src="http://quicksale.themerex.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/home-m-3.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><span>Title of Image</span></figcaption></figure> </div> Purchasing products from ThemeRex means entrusting your reputation to one of the best web-studios. ThemeRex company does its work with its customer in mind. That is why you are getting the best product that will perfectly suit your needs.</p>
<p>Not only does ThemeRex create bright, eye-catching designs and do premium quality code, they provide great support to their customers. ThemeRex technical support is always there to assist their users with all their technical questions regarding ThemeRex products. We speak clear language understood by everyone. You need our assistance &#8211; we happily help you. Use comments to ask pre-sale questions, and Ticket System to get any help with our products. Our support team is always happy to help our customers. Whether it is assistance with installation or just configuration, we are here to help.  </p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/new-post-with-image/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>House Market Indicators</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/house-market-indicators/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/house-market-indicators/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 11:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Living room]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=642</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[In attempting to identify bubbles before they burst, economists have developed a number of financial ratios and economic indicators that can be used to evaluate whether homes in a given area are fairly valued. By comparing current levels to previous levels that have proven unsustainable in the past (i.e. led to or at least accompanied [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In attempting to identify bubbles before they burst, economists have developed a number of financial ratios and economic indicators that can be used to evaluate whether homes in a given area are fairly valued. By comparing current levels to previous levels that have proven unsustainable in the past (i.e. led to or at least accompanied crashes), one can make an educated guess as to whether a given real estate market is experiencing a bubble. Indicators describe two interwoven aspects of housing bubble: a valuation component and a debt (or leverage) component. The valuation component measures how expensive houses are relative to what most people can afford, and the debt component measures how indebted households become in buying them for home or profit (and also how much exposure the banks accumulate by lending for them). </p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/house-market-indicators/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gallery Post Format</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/gallery-post-format/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/gallery-post-format/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2014 11:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style Large]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style Small]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cottage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Attic]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=532</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Don’t be afraid of multiple offers. You still have some control. There are a few things that can happen if you get into competition. The seller can accept your offer and you will have bought a house. Or the seller can accept someone else’s offer and you need to keep looking. Or the seller can [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[ 
<a href='http://quicksale.themerex.net/shortcodes/home-13/'><img width="200" height="200" src="http://quicksale.themerex.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/home-13-200x200.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail" alt="home-13" /></a>
<a href='http://quicksale.themerex.net/?attachment_id=3129'><img width="200" height="200" src="http://quicksale.themerex.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/home-6-200x200.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail" alt="home-6" /></a>
<a href='http://quicksale.themerex.net/?attachment_id=3124'><img width="200" height="200" src="http://quicksale.themerex.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/home-1-200x200.jpg" class="attachment-thumbnail" alt="home-1" /></a>
 Don’t be afraid of multiple offers. You still have some control. There are a few things that can happen if you get into competition. The seller can accept your offer and you will have bought a house. Or the seller can accept someone else’s offer and you need to keep looking. Or the seller can work with your offer, and sign it back to you with a counter-offer that you can accept or decline, and perhaps even counter-offer back to them.</p>
<h4>Taking Charge in a Bidding War</h4>
<p>There is another scenario that I despise, but unfortunately it happens: the seller has a number of offers on the table, and decides to send them all back for improvement. Personally, I think they should just choose the best one and accept it or work with it. In the case where you are sent back to improve, you have control and choices. The seller is actually at risk if the offer is signed back to you and a higher figure is requested. You can simply walk away from the deal, as you are not obligated to increase your money or change any terms of the agreement. You can resubmit your offer as is, or you can make some improvements to the offer by way of increasing the money or removing a condition or changing any term on the contract that the seller wasn’t happy about.</p>
<p>Just remember, although emotions run high and it’s not the most fun scenario for buyers, you should keep your head about you, and understand that you are always in control.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/gallery-post-format/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Mortgage In Your 50s</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/a-mortgage-in-your-50s/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/a-mortgage-in-your-50s/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 11:52:23 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style Small]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=644</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It’s not hard to find a 50-something asking the question, “Am I too old to buy a home?” The answer is, absolutely not. A couple of decades ago, the assumption was that everybody retired around age 60 or 65, but today, three out of four Americans plan to work past retirement age. In other words, [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It’s not hard to find a 50-something asking the question, “Am I too old to buy a home?” The answer is, absolutely not. A couple of decades ago, the assumption was that everybody retired around age 60 or 65, but today, three out of four Americans plan to work past retirement age. In other words, at 50, you probably still have many working years left, and that means income to put towards a home. That doesn’t mean that you should forget about age. You’re not 20 anymore (thank goodness). Financial decisions are a little more complicated in some ways, but easier in others. If you’re considering purchasing a home in your 50s, think through these issues.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/a-mortgage-in-your-50s/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Steps To Buy A Home</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/steps-to-buy-a-home/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/steps-to-buy-a-home/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 13:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style Small]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Attic]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=492</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[First of all, have your credit checked. Homebuyers to have their credit checked six months before buying a place to make sure their FICO score is where it needs to be. Know what you can afford. Realtors insist that prospective homebuyers “contact a lender and be pre-approved so they know the price of the house [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>First of all, have your credit checked. Homebuyers to have their credit checked six months before buying a place to make sure their FICO score is where it needs to be.<br />
Know what you can afford. Realtors insist that prospective homebuyers “contact a lender and be pre-approved so they know the price of the house they can afford and won’t be disappointed that they can’t go into the price range they were originally considering.” According to many agents, most people don’t get pre-approved, which usually winds up wasting time and causing problems down the line.<br />
Look into location. If you’re going to be in this home for any length of time, look into school districts and other things that may not matter to you yet, but could eventually. Also, find out what your city or county taxes would be, as well as if your community has Homeowners’ or Condo Association dues.<br />
Think twice before buying a home on your own. Buying a home requires real estate and legal savvy, as well as the confidence to negotiate the final price.<br />
Have the house inspected. Once you find a place, have a home inspection done to find out what is wrong with the place. Even if the person isn’t going to fix it, you need to know that before you make the decision to buy the house.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/steps-to-buy-a-home/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Are You Ready to Rent?</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/are-you-ready-to-rent/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/are-you-ready-to-rent/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 13:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style Large]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style Small]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cottage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Driveway]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=491</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Although you may feel ready to get out on your own, make sure your finances are in order before you take the leap. Take a look at some rental listings in the areas in which you are interested in living and get an idea of how much you&#8217;ll have to pay to live there. If [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Although you may feel ready to get out on your own, make sure your finances are in order before you take the leap. Take a look at some rental listings in the areas in which you are interested in living and get an idea of how much you&#8217;ll have to pay to live there. If you are already making payments on a car, credit card or student loan, be sure to include these amounts in your expenses list. Gas for your car (or a bus pass), insurance (rental and vehicle), cell phone bills and an estimate of the amount you usually spend on personal items should also be included.</p>
<h4>Find a Place You Can Call Home</h4>
<p>Once you have set some parameters in terms of what you can afford, it&#8217;s time to start looking for a place to move into. Start by searching internet sites, classified ads and by visiting the neighborhoods where you might like to live. Whether you decide to rent month-to-month or sign a year-long lease, be sure to read what you are agreeing to carefully. The lease should detail how much rent you must pay, when it is due, how long you can occupy the apartment or house and who is responsible for utilities (some leases include them). It will also include rules about pets, roommates and whether you can paint or do improvements. <div id="sc_slider_315668435" class="sc_slider sc_slider_swiper sc_slider_controls sc_slider_pagination sc_alignleft swiper-slider-container" data-interval="5000" style="height:230px;width:50%;"><ul class="slides swiper-wrapper"><li class="swiper-slide" style="background-image:url(http://quicksale.themerex.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/home-5-344x230.jpg);width:50%;height:230px;"><a href="http://quicksale.themerex.net/new-post-with-image/" title="New Post With Image"></a></li><li class="swiper-slide" style="background-image:url(http://quicksale.themerex.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/home-12-346x230.jpg);width:50%;height:230px;"><a href="http://quicksale.themerex.net/are-you-ready-to-rent/" title="Are You Ready to Rent?"></a></li><li class="swiper-slide" style="background-image:url(http://quicksale.themerex.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/03/home-4-353x230.jpg);width:50%;height:230px;"><a href="http://quicksale.themerex.net/is-condo-life-for-you/" title="Is Condo Life For You?"></a></li></ul>
					<ul class="flex-direction-nav">
					<li><a class="flex-prev" href="#"></a></li>
					<li><a class="flex-next" href="#"></a></li>
					</ul><div class="flex-control-nav"></div></div> If you&#8217;ve done everything right, your utilities should be hooked up, your bags packed and your bills paid. Determine what day you will be moving into your new place. If possible, recruit friends and family to help you move, rather than hiring a mover. The transition to making it on your own may not be simple, but if you do it right, you can avoid having to retreat to your parents&#8217; basement. Plus, you&#8217;ll develop the skills you need to improve your standard of living as you go along.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/are-you-ready-to-rent/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Condo Life For You?</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/is-condo-life-for-you/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/is-condo-life-for-you/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 09:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style Small]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cottage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Living room]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=457</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[There are a many benefits to owning your own condo &#8211; chief among them the fact that you actually own your own condo! However, along with the benefits, there can be unforeseen hassles. For example, a condo can be more than a financial commitment; it&#8217;s a social commitment as well. In this article we&#8217;ll examine [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are a many benefits to owning your own condo &#8211; chief among them the fact that you actually own your own condo! However, along with the benefits, there can be unforeseen hassles. For example, a condo can be more than a financial commitment; it&#8217;s a social commitment as well. In this article we&#8217;ll examine these considerations to make sure that your new condo life is a great one. If you are thinking about making a purchase in the near future, don&#8217;t forget to consider the ways condo living could affect your life. <blockquote class="sc_quote  margin_bottom_mini sc_quote_style_1" style="margin-top:5px;"><p>Always bear in mind that your own resolution to succeed is more important than any other.</p></blockquote> Costs for the condo owner usually don&#8217;t stop at the mortgage. You&#8217;ll also have to think about things like monthly owner fees, sometimes called condo association fees, and homeowner&#8217;s insurance. The association fees pay for things such as general upkeep and insurance of the condo complex. If the gate to your complex&#8217;s parking garage breaks, the fees you and your neighbors pay will go toward fixing it. These fees also pay for the condo&#8217;s insurance, which covers major situations that affect the complex as a whole. It&#8217;s important to note that these fees never go away.</p>
<h4>The Social Setting</h4>
<p>When you&#8217;re in buying mode, it&#8217;s common to think only in terms of dollars and cents &#8211; a condo is a huge purchase, after all. But it&#8217;s essential not to forget the social aspect of living in a condo. Different complexes work well for different kinds of people, so get to know your complex as well as your prospective neighbors to make sure that they&#8217;re a good fit for you &#8211; if you&#8217;re easing into retirement, it might not be a great idea to buy a condo next to a bunch of hard-partying college kids or vice versa. <div class="sc_section sc_alignleft columns1_2" style="margin-top:5px !important;margin-bottom:10px !important;"> <figure class="sc_image  sc_image_shape_square"><img src="http://quicksale.themerex.net/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/home-m-3.jpg" alt="" /><figcaption><span>Title of Image</span></figcaption></figure> </div> When you buy your condo, you might find that you&#8217;re not happy with certain aspects of the bylaws. If this is the case, there are ways to get things done without causing too much of a ripple. The best way to get your voice heard is to sit in on homeowners&#8217; meetings for your complex. At these meetings, the governing body of the complex will get together to discuss issues that have come up. <br style="clear:both" /> &nbsp;<br />
<a href="#">Conclusion</a> Don&#8217;t pack up that moving van just yet &#8211; condos can be a great place to live, but only if you spend the time to look into what life will be like in your future complex. Don&#8217;t let unexpected speed bumps, such as condo association fees and bylaws, keep your condo life from being the good life.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/is-condo-life-for-you/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Selling Your House?</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/selling-your-house/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/selling-your-house/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 13:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cottage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kitchen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=327</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The peak homebuying season may be over, but there are still steps you can take to ensure a speedy sale. Setting the right price and making an excellent first impression are both essential to attracting buyers, but what else can you do to get the offers rolling in? Here are 10 tips to help you [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The peak homebuying season may be over, but there are still steps you can take to ensure a speedy sale. Setting the right price and making an excellent first impression are both essential to attracting buyers, but what else can you do to get the offers rolling in? Here are 10 tips to help you sell your home as quickly as possible – even in the offseason.<br />
<strong>Price it right from the start.</strong> Sellers often think they should start the asking price high and then lower it later if the house fails to sell. But that can result in a slower sale – sometimes even at a lower price. The first 30 days’ activity of your house being on the market is always the best activity you’re going to see.<br />
<strong>Update the interior and exterior.</strong> New fixtures, fresh paint and updated landscaping are all fairly easy and affordable ways to give your home a makeover. It’s got to look up to the current market conditions and what’s in style.<br />
<strong>Stage the house to show how the rooms are supposed to be used.</strong> If you have odd rooms with no obvious role, give them one. An odd alcove off the kitchen could be staged as an office or a pantry, for example.<br />
<strong>Make the property easy to show.</strong> The more flexible you are about visits, the more people will be able to see your home. Be ready for prospective visitors early in the morning, at night and on weekends, with little notice. Also, leave when the house is shown so would-be buyers can feel free to move about without feeling like intruders and discuss the home&#8217;s pros and cons honestly.<br />
<strong>Make sure your listing is on all the major online portals.</strong> This is usually part of an agent’s service, but it doesn’t hurt to double-check that your listing is on the largest real estate websites. It also helps if your agent showcases the home on social media. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/selling-your-house/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top Mortgage Mistakes</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/top-mortgage-mistakes/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/top-mortgage-mistakes/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 09:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style Small]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Attic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kitchen]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=654</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[During the 2007-2009 financial crisis, the United States economy crumbled because of a problem with mortgage foreclosures. Borrowers all over the nation had trouble paying their mortgages. At the time, eight out of 10 borrowers were trying to refinance their mortgages. Even high end homeowners were having trouble with foreclosures. Why were so many citizens [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>During the 2007-2009 financial crisis, the United States economy crumbled because of a problem with mortgage foreclosures. Borrowers all over the nation had trouble paying their mortgages. At the time, eight out of 10 borrowers were trying to refinance their mortgages. Even high end homeowners were having trouble with foreclosures. Why were so many citizens having trouble with their mortgages? Let&#8217;s take a look at the biggest mortgage mistakes that homeowners make.</p>
<p><strong>1. Adjustable Rate Mortgages</strong><br />
Adjustable rate mortgages seem like a homeowners dream. An adjustable rate mortgage starts you off with a low interest rate for the first two to five years. They allow you to buy a larger house than you can normally qualify for and have lower payments that you can afford. After two to five years the interest rate resets to a higher market rate. That&#8217;s no problem because borrowers can just take the equity out of their homes and refinance to a lower rate once it resets.</p>
<p>Well, it doesn&#8217;t always work out that way. When housing prices drop, borrowers tend to find that they are unable to refinance their existing loans. This leaves many borrowers facing high mortgage payments that are two to three times their original payments. The dream of home ownership quickly becomes a nightmare.</p>
<p><strong>2. No Down Payment</strong><br />
During the subprime crisis, many companies were offering borrowers no down payment loans to borrowers. The purpose of a down payment is twofold. First, it increases the amount of equity that you have in your home and reduces the amount of money that you owe on a home. Second, a down payment makes sure that you have some skin in the game. Borrowers that place down a large down payment are much more likely to try everything possible to make their mortgage payments since they do not want to lose their investment. Many borrowers who put little to nothing down on their homes find themselves upside down on their mortgage and end up just walking away. They owe more money than the home is worth. The more a borrower owes, the more likely they are to walk away.</p>
<p><strong>3. Liar Loans</strong><br />
The phrase &#8220;liar loans&#8221; leaves a bad taste in your mouth. Liar loans were incredibly popular during the real estate boom prior to the subprime meltdown that began in 2007. Mortgage lenders were quick to hand them out and borrowers were quick to accept them. A liar loan is a loan that requires little to no documentation. Liar loans do not require verification. The loan is based on the borrower&#8217;s stated income, stated assets and stated expenses.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/top-mortgage-mistakes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Real Estate Derivatives</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/real-estate-derivatives/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/real-estate-derivatives/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 09:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Style Small]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Attic]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=655</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[A real estate derivative is a financial instrument whose value is based on the price of real estate. The core uses for real estate derivatives are: hedging positions, pre-investing assets and re-allocating a portfolio. The major products within real estate derivatives are: swaps, futures contracts, options (calls and puts) and structured products. Each of these [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A real estate derivative is a financial instrument whose value is based on the price of real estate. The core uses for real estate derivatives are: hedging positions, pre-investing assets and re-allocating a portfolio. The major products within real estate derivatives are: swaps, futures contracts, options (calls and puts) and structured products. Each of these products can use a different real estate index. Further, each property type and region can be used as a reference point for any real estate derivative. </p>
<p>The most basic form of real estate derivative is a swap transaction, in which one investor, or one side, goes long and the other side goes short (finance). An investor would want to execute a swap if they thought that the market, or sector, was likely to appreciate, in which case they would go long. Alternatively, if an investor’s view was that the market would depreciate from that point, they would go short, or take the other side of that trade.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/real-estate-derivatives/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
