<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Quick Sale &#187; 4 Columns fullscreen</title>
	<atom:link href="http://quicksale.themerex.net/category/portfolio-grid/portfolio-4-columns-fullscreen/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net</link>
	<description>single property</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 07:37:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=4.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Moving House</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/moving-house/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/moving-house/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 14:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=815</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[How do you move everything you own into your new home without losing your mind? By reading our moving home guides. Handy hints and tips to help you pack up and settle in.. Choosing a Removal Company. Moving items out of your current property and into your new home takes a great deal of organisation, [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How do you move everything you own into your new home without losing your mind? By reading our moving home guides. Handy hints and tips to help you pack up and settle in..</p>
<p><strong>Choosing a Removal Company.</strong> Moving items out of your current property and into your new home takes a great deal of organisation, time and physical strength. If you’ve got a lot of boxes, fragile items, valuables or heavy pieces of furniture to move, then appointing a professional removal company is a worthwhile investment. And it’s crucial you find the removal company that’s right for you.</p>
<p><strong>House Packing.</strong> House packing is a tiring and time-consuming affair. We can’t say packing your life into boxes is ever going to be a pleasure but heed our practical tips and advice and you could save your sanity, as well as your fragile possessions.</p>
<p><strong>Moving Day.</strong> It’s finally here. The day you’ve been longing for and dreading at the same time. Moving day can be one of the most stressful days of your life. So follow our guide to make the big day as hassle-free and exciting as it should be.</p>
<p><strong>Involve your children before the move.</strong> Giving children tasks and responsibility will give them control over their situation.  Involve them in packing and let them pack up their own toys.  Also encourage them to de-clutter and get rid of toys they no longer play with . Make sure that children’s toys are the last items to be packed onto the van and are therefore easily accessed at the other end. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/moving-house/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Renting to Own</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/renting-to-own/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/renting-to-own/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 14:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basement]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=821</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Rent-to-own, also known as rental-purchase, is a type of legally documented transaction under which tangible property, such as furniture, consumer electronics and home appliances, is leased in exchange for a weekly or monthly payment, with the option to purchase at some point during the agreement. A rent-to-own transaction differs from a traditional lease, in that [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Rent-to-own, also known as rental-purchase, is a type of legally documented transaction under which tangible property, such as furniture, consumer electronics and home appliances, is leased in exchange for a weekly or monthly payment, with the option to purchase at some point during the agreement.</p>
<p>A rent-to-own transaction differs from a traditional lease, in that the lessee can purchase the leased item at any time during the agreement (in a traditional lease the lessee has no such right), and from a hire purchase/installment plan, in that the lessee can terminate the agreement by simply returning the property (in a hire purchase the buyer has a limited time, if any, to cancel the agreement).</p>
<p>The usage of rent-to-own transactions began in the United Kingdom and Europe, and first appeared in the United States during the 1950s and 1960s. While rent-to-own terminology is most commonly associated with consumer goods transactions, the term is sometimes used in connection with real estate transactions.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/renting-to-own/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buy or Sell First?</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/buy-or-sell-first/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/buy-or-sell-first/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 14:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=823</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Most people sell their current home at the same time as buying a new one, forming a property chain. Selling before you buy has risks, but it can also have great advantages Advantages of selling before you buy Disadvantages Tips If you do sell before you buy, make sure as many things as possible (mortgage [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Most people sell their current home at the same time as buying a new one, forming a property chain. Selling before you buy has risks, but it can also have great advantages</p>
<p><strong>Advantages of selling before you buy</strong> <ul class="sc_list sc_list_style_ul"> <li class="sc_list_item odd first">It puts you in a stronger position when buying. The seller you want to buy from would almost certainly prefer a buyer who has the cash in the bank (and/or a pre-approved mortgage) rather than enter a chain, where their sale is dependent upon you finding someone to buy your house</li> <li class="sc_list_item even">You are less likely to be gazumped. If you put in a decent offer the buyer is unlikely to take another if it means entering a property chain</li> <li class="sc_list_item odd">You remain in control of the sale of your own house – because you won’t need to make a quick sale, you will not be pressurized into selling cheaply</li> <li class="sc_list_item even">Those with time on their side are usually in the strongest negotiating position</li> <li class="sc_list_item odd">You will know exactly how much you can spend because you’ll have the money from your sale in the bank – buying your new home won’t be dependent on you achieving the expected price on your existing one</li> <li class="sc_list_item even">If prices are falling, then houses get more affordable as you wait</li> </ul> <strong>Disadvantages</strong> <ul class="sc_list sc_list_style_ul"> <li class="sc_list_item odd first">If you sell first, expecting to be able to buy quickly after, you may be disappointed and instead have to rent for a time, which can prove very costly</li> <li class="sc_list_item even">If prices are rising fast, by the time you’ve sold your house and sorted out somewhere to rent, a new house will be much less affordable. For example, if you rent for a year, and prices rise by 10% in that year, then you will only be able to afford 10% less</li> <li class="sc_list_item odd">Renting can be stressful, but being in a chain, being gazumped, or feeling you’ve undersold can be worse.</li> </ul> <strong>Tips</strong><br />
If you do sell before you buy, make sure as many things as possible (mortgage etc) are organized beforehand so you can buy quickly<br />
Do your research before you sell. Decide what area you want to buy in, and what sort of property you want to buy. Keep an eye on the property market while you are selling just in case that perfect house comes along. You’ve got time so you might as well use it. Develop relationships with a number of estate agents before you sell, so that you get in there first with all good properties that come up for sale. Get your mortgage pre-approved. This will make you even more attractive to a seller. Try and slow down the selling process, by agreeing a longish period between agreeing an offer and exchanging, and between exchanging and completion. This might give you enough time to buy a new place in the meanwhile.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/buy-or-sell-first/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cash Vs. Mortgage</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/cash-vs-mortgage/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/cash-vs-mortgage/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 14:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=819</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Paying cash for a home eliminates the need to pay interest on the loan and many closing costs. When buying a house with cash, there are no mortgage origination fees, appraisal fees or other fees charged by lenders to assess buyers. A cash home purchase also has the flexibility of closing faster (if desired) than [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Paying cash for a home eliminates the need to pay interest on the loan and many closing costs. When buying a house with cash, there are no mortgage origination fees, appraisal fees or other fees charged by lenders to assess buyers. A cash home purchase also has the flexibility of closing faster (if desired) than one requiring financing, which could be attractive to a seller. Those benefits to the seller shouldn’t come without a price. Also, a cash buyer’s home is not leveraged, which allows a homeowner to sell the house more easily – even at a loss – regardless of market conditions.</p>
<p>Obtaining financing also has significant benefits. Even if a buyer has the ability to pay cash for a home, it might make sense to not tie up a lot of cash to purchase real estate. Doing so could tie your hands down the road. Cash buyers need to be sure to leave to leave themselves plenty of liquidity. If the home requires major repairs or renovations, it may be tough to obtain a home equity mortgage down the road as you don’t know what your credit score will look like in the future, how much the home will then be worth or other factors that determine approval for a mortgage. Selling a home bought with cash could also be a problem if the owners stretched a lot financially to buy it. Paying cash also has tax implications. Not having a mortgage could also negate a homestead exemption if you find yourself seriously in debt in the future. Most states grant consumers a certain level of protection from creditors regarding their home. </p>
<p>The best advice when considering which option makes the most sense is to opt for the choice that gives you the bigger bang for your buck. Also ask yourself which will provide the greater return on your investment.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/cash-vs-mortgage/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>First Property Search</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/first-property-search/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/first-property-search/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 14:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basement]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=814</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Moving to your own place? If you’re renting for the first time follow Shelter’s top tips to avoid the common pitfalls. Be sure it&#8217;s safe Check the gas safety certificate before you move in. You should also make sure you’re happy with the general condition of the property before you sign an agreement. Check that [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Moving to your own place? If you’re renting for the first time follow Shelter’s top tips to avoid the common pitfalls.</p>
<p><strong>Be sure it&#8217;s safe</strong><br />
Check the gas safety certificate before you move in. You should also make sure you’re happy with the general condition of the property before you sign an agreement.</p>
<p><strong>Check that your deposit will be protected</strong><br />
Landlords must protect your deposit within 30 days after they’ve received it and must give you full details of which scheme is protecting it and how you can get it back. Use Shelter’s deposit checker tool to make sure your deposit has been protected – it just takes 3 minutes.</p>
<p>M<strong>ake sure the inventory is accurate</strong><br />
When you move in check and agree with the landlord or agent the list of contents in the property and any existing damage. You could also take your own photos when moving in and moving out. This is the best way to avoid disputes later on. Finally, make sure you have the right contact details for your landlord.</p>
<p><strong>Know your own responsibilities</strong><br />
Renters have obligations too. Your duties as a renter include paying rent and bills on time and not disturbing your neighbours.</p>
<p><strong>Moving in with a mate?</strong><br />
Signing a joint tenancy with your housemates or having individual tenancy agreements with the landlord can have a big impact on your rights. Check that you understand the agreement you have.</p>
<p><strong>Landlord wants to increase the rent?</strong><br />
Your landlord can increase the rent but only at certain times or if s/he is offering you a new agreement, depending on what type of tenancy you have. Check what tenancy type you have on this tenancy checker.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/first-property-search/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Home Inspection</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/the-home-inspection/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/the-home-inspection/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 14:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Attic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basement]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=813</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[A home inspection is a limited, non-invasive examination of the condition of a home, often in connection with the sale of that home. Home inspections are usually conducted by a home inspector who has the training and certifications to perform such inspections. The inspector prepares and delivers to the client a written report of findings. [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A home inspection is a limited, non-invasive examination of the condition of a home, often in connection with the sale of that home. Home inspections are usually conducted by a home inspector who has the training and certifications to perform such inspections. The inspector prepares and delivers to the client a written report of findings. The client then uses the knowledge gained to make informed decisions about their pending real estate purchase. The home inspector describes the condition of the home at the time of inspection but does not guarantee future condition, efficiency, or life expectancy of systems or components.</p>
<p>A home inspector is sometimes confused with a real estate appraiser. A home inspector determines the condition of a structure, whereas an appraiser determines the value of a property. In the United States, although not all states or municipalities regulate home inspectors, there are various professional associations for home inspectors that provide education, training, and networking opportunities. A professional home inspection is an examination of the current condition of a house. It is not an inspection to verify compliance with appropriate codes; building inspection is a term often used for building code compliance inspections in the United States. A similar but more complicated inspection of commercial buildings is a property condition assessment. Home inspections identify problems but building diagnostics identifies solutions to the found problems and there predicted outcomes.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/the-home-inspection/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buying Hints &amp; Insights</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/buying-hints-insights/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/buying-hints-insights/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 14:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=812</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Buying a house can be a daunting task, even for someone who has owned several homes. Here aresome helpful hints for the first time property buyers:]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Buying a house can be a daunting task, even for someone who has owned several homes. Here aresome helpful hints for the first time property buyers: <ol class="sc_list sc_list_style_ol"> <li class="sc_list_item odd first">Use your online resources. Almost every state and local government has a website where you can research real estate information. The data on home sales, taxes, and neighborhoods is invaluable when you are shopping for a home.</li> <li class="sc_list_item even">Be realistic about how much you can spend.Try to buy a home in a price range that allows you to put down 20%. If you put down less than this, you will have to pay PMI (private mortgage insurance) to protect the lender in case you default on the loan.</li> <li class="sc_list_item odd">Shop for a home in the winter, preferably around the holidays. Since most people just aren&#8217;t interested in buying a home whenthey are trying to deal with the holidays, you can pretty much be one of the few buyers out there.</li> <li class="sc_list_item even">Always have a home inspection. Most people know this fact already, but it is really important in areas with a hot real estate market. It can be easy to get caught up in bidding wars, and to want to get a house at all costs</li> </ol> ]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/buying-hints-insights/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Working With A Realtor</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/working-with-a-realtor/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/working-with-a-realtor/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 14:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Attic]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=799</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[A Realtor is a broker or agent who is a member of the Board of Realtors, an organization that follows a code of ethics beyond state license laws. It is realtors who sponsor the Multiple Listing Service to which every real estate agent in the country is beholden for listing or searching prospects. Shopping for [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Realtor is a broker or agent who is a member of the Board of Realtors, an organization that follows a code of ethics beyond state license laws. It is realtors who sponsor the Multiple Listing Service to which every real estate agent in the country is beholden for listing or searching prospects. Shopping for a real estate agent should be no different from searching for any other professional, like a lawyer or an accountant. If you know someone in the business &#8211; such as an escrow officer, title representative, or homeowners&#8217; insurance salesperson &#8211; ask for a recommendation. When interviewing prospective agents, ask questions about the local market and expect informed answers on the spot. If they have to call you back after they check the listings, it could be they&#8217;re not doing due diligence.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/working-with-a-realtor/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Home For The 1st Time</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/home-for-the-1st-time/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/home-for-the-1st-time/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 14:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basement]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=798</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Moving to your own place? If you’re renting for the first time follow Shelter’s top tips to avoid the common pitfalls. Be sure it&#8217;s safe Check the gas safety certificate before you move in. You should also make sure you’re happy with the general condition of the property before you sign an agreement. Check that [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Moving to your own place? If you’re renting for the first time follow Shelter’s top tips to avoid the common pitfalls.</p>
<p><strong>Be sure it&#8217;s safe</strong><br />
Check the gas safety certificate before you move in. You should also make sure you’re happy with the general condition of the property before you sign an agreement.</p>
<p><strong>Check that your deposit will be protected</strong><br />
Landlords must protect your deposit within 30 days after they’ve received it and must give you full details of which scheme is protecting it and how you can get it back. Use Shelter’s deposit checker tool to make sure your deposit has been protected – it just takes 3 minutes.</p>
<p>M<strong>ake sure the inventory is accurate</strong><br />
When you move in check and agree with the landlord or agent the list of contents in the property and any existing damage. You could also take your own photos when moving in and moving out. This is the best way to avoid disputes later on. Finally, make sure you have the right contact details for your landlord.</p>
<p><strong>Know your own responsibilities</strong><br />
Renters have obligations too. Your duties as a renter include paying rent and bills on time and not disturbing your neighbours.</p>
<p><strong>Moving in with a mate?</strong><br />
Signing a joint tenancy with your housemates or having individual tenancy agreements with the landlord can have a big impact on your rights. Check that you understand the agreement you have.</p>
<p><strong>Landlord wants to increase the rent?</strong><br />
Your landlord can increase the rent but only at certain times or if s/he is offering you a new agreement, depending on what type of tenancy you have. Check what tenancy type you have on this tenancy checker.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/home-for-the-1st-time/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Step-by-Step Buying</title>
		<link>http://quicksale.themerex.net/step-by-step-home-buying/</link>
		<comments>http://quicksale.themerex.net/step-by-step-home-buying/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 14:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[1 Column]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1 Column + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns + sidebar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[4 Columns fullscreen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grid Alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Classic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Portfolio Grid]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://quicksale.themerex.net/?p=795</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[First of all, have your credit checked. Homebuyers to have their credit checked six months before buying a place to make sure their FICO score is where it needs to be. Know what you can afford. Realtors insist that prospective homebuyers “contact a lender and be pre-approved so they know the price of the house [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>First of all, have your credit checked. Homebuyers to have their credit checked six months before buying a place to make sure their FICO score is where it needs to be.<br />
Know what you can afford. Realtors insist that prospective homebuyers “contact a lender and be pre-approved so they know the price of the house they can afford and won’t be disappointed that they can’t go into the price range they were originally considering.” According to many agents, most people don’t get pre-approved, which usually winds up wasting time and causing problems down the line.<br />
Look into location. If you’re going to be in this home for any length of time, look into school districts and other things that may not matter to you yet, but could eventually. Also, find out what your city or county taxes would be, as well as if your community has Homeowners’ or Condo Association dues.<br />
Think twice before buying a home on your own. Buying a home requires real estate and legal savvy, as well as the confidence to negotiate the final price.<br />
Have the house inspected. Once you find a place, have a home inspection done to find out what is wrong with the place. Even if the person isn’t going to fix it, you need to know that before you make the decision to buy the house.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://quicksale.themerex.net/step-by-step-home-buying/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
